你们男生不懂
What you guys don't understand is
亲吻对女生的重要性
for us, kissing is as important as any part of it.
没错
Yeah, right.
真的?
You serious?
真的
Oh, yeah.
初吻可以让你明白一切
Everything you need to know is in that first kiss.
当然      就是 我觉得对于男生
Absolutely.        Yeah, I think, for us
接吻很大程度上像是序幕!
kissing is pretty much like an opening act.
像是你听Pink Floyd的音乐会之前不得不忍受的
I mean, it's like the standup comedian you have to sit through.
笑星们的表演一样
before Pink Floyd comes out.
对 我们并非讨厌脱口秀
Yeah, and it's not that we don't like the comedian.
但那不是
It's just that that's not...
我们买票的原因
...why we bought the ticket.
问题出在于
See, the problem is, though
演唱会结束后 不论表演有多精采
after the concert's over, no matter how great the show was
你们女生总还想再看脱口秀
you girls are always looking for the comedian again.
我们在车上奋力杀出车阵
I mean, we're in the car, we're fighting traffic
只是拼命让自己别睡着
basically just trying to stay awake.
是哦 给你一个建议 叫脱口秀主持人再度上场
Yeah, well, word of advice: Bring back the comedian.
否则下次
Otherwise, you're gonna find yourself
你们只能独自坐家里听唱片
sitting at home listening to that album alone.
我们还在谈论性吗?
Are we still talking about sex?
【海盗美剧 友情制作】
-== http://www.hdmeiju.com ==-
新浪微博：@海盗美剧
《老友记》蓝光版 第01季 第02集
字幕来源：射手网      重新调校：寒 枫@海盗美剧
英文编辑：林奇先生
不 这样很好
No, it's good. It is good.
只是她看起来是不是有点烦恼吗?
It's just that, doesn't she seem a little angry?
她有麻烦事
Well, she has issues.
她有吗?
Does she?
他在外头乱搞女人
He's out banging other women over the head with a club
而她却待家里设法去除地毯上乳齿象的味道
while she sits at home trying to get the mastodon smell out of the carpet.
玛莎 他们是穴居人
Marsha, see, these are cave people.
他们关心的问题是
Okay, they have issues like:
冰河愈来愈接近了 懂吗?
"Gee, that glacier's getting kind of close." See?
谈到问题 那不是你前妻吗?
Speaking of issues, isn't that your exwife?
我的?不是      是的,她是 嘿,你好
My...no, no.        Yes, it is. Carol, hi.
是的,她是
Okay. Yes. Yes, it is.
我到冰河期找你怎么样?
How about I'll catch up with you in the Ice Age?
嗨!     嗨!
Hi.      Hi.
那么
So...
你的气色好极了
You look great.
我讨厌看到这样
I hate that.
抱歉 谢了 你的气色也很好
Sorry. Thanks. You look good too.
在这儿任何人都
Well, you know, in here, anyone who
能直立...
stands erect
最近如何?还是...女同志?
So, what's new? Still a...A lesbian?
呃
Well
想问就问!
You never know.
最近呃家庭生活如何?
How's, um? How's the family?
玛蒂仍然神经兮兮的
Marty's still totally paranoid.
喔, 卡萝      你为何来这儿?
Oh, and...     Carol, why are you here, Carol?
我怀孕了       怀孕
I'm pregnant.         Pregnant.
喔 看那 她似乎不急着离开
Oh. Looks like she didn't leave in such a hurry after all.
人和人 让人讨厌的就是有
I think this is the episode of Three's Company
误会
where's there's some kind of misunderstanding.
我看过这一集
Then I've already seen this one.
喝完没?谢谢
Are you through with that? Thanks.
抱歉 吞下去的时间太慢
Yeah, sorry, the swallowing slowed me down.
这是谁的小纸团?
Whose little ball of paper is this?
我的
Oh, that would be mine.
我写给自己一张便条 后来觉得自己不需要
See, I wrote a note to myself, then I didn't need it.
于是将它揉成纸团 我现在不想活了!
So I balled it up and now I wish I was dead.
她已经拍松过那个枕头
She already fluffed that pillow.
摩妮卡 你已经拍过了枕头了
Monica, you know, you already fluffed...
但是它很好
But it's fine.
抱歉 各位
Look, I'm sorry.
我只是不想 让他们有藉题发挥的机会
I don't want to give them any more ammunition than they have.
没错 我们都知道 父母对孩子的枕头
Yes, we know how cruel a parent can be
要求有多苛刻
about the flatness of a child's pillow.
摩妮卡?      嗨
Monica?        Hi.
摩妮卡 你吓到我了
Monica,um,you're scaring me.
你慌慌张张的
I mean, you're, like, all chaotic and twirly, you know?
而且显得不是很好
Not in a good way.
冷静
Yeah, calm down.
你没见过每次他们来时 罗斯慌张的样子
You don't see Ross getting all chaotic and twirly every time they come.
因为在我爸妈心目中 罗斯不可能犯错
That's because, as far as my parents are concerned, Ross can do no wrong.
他是个王子
You see, he's the prince.
显然 他们在我出生前有个大型仪式
Apparently they had some big ceremony before I was born.
嘘
Ew, ew, ew.
怎么了?      丑陋裸男有个"美腿器"
What?        Ugly Naked Guy got a ThighMaster.
呃
Ew.
有人看见我的订婚戒指吗?      有 它真漂亮
Has anybody seen my engagement ring?        Yeah, it's beautiful.
糟了 糟了
Oh, God. Oh, God.
哦 天呐       不要动它们
Oh, God, oh, God, oh, God.         No, don't touch that.
明天就要还他戒指 我似乎还不够担心
Oh, like I wasn't dreading tomorrow enough having to give it back to him.
巴瑞 记得我吗? 我是那个
"Hi, Barry, remember me? I'm the girl
让你在亲友面前出糗的人
that stomped on your heart in front of your entire family"
天啊 如今我必须还他戒指 戒指却不见了
Oh, God. Now I'm gonna have to return the ring, without the ring
叫我如何面对他!
which makes it so much harder.
别急 我们会找到的 对不?
Easy, Rach, we'll find it. Won't we?
哦 必须滴      好的 想想
Oh,yeah.        Okay,look
你最后记得它是什么时候?
When did you have it on last?
"孩仔" 大概是在遗失之前
Doy. Probably right before she lost it.
这年头说"孩仔"的人不多
You don't get a lot of "doy" these days.
我今天早上还戴它
I know I had it this morning.
我在厨房戴着做...
I know I had it when I was in the kitchen with
面条?
Dinah?
别生气
Oh, don't be mad.
你做的好事?       对不起
You didn't.         Oh, I'm sorry.
我只给了你一件事干! （你却把它搞砸了!）
I gave you one job.
你看面条现在变得多直
Oh, but look how straight those noodles are.
摩妮卡  在意大利面中找订婚戒指不是那样找的
Monica, you know that's not how you look for an engagement ring in a lasagna.
我办不到
I just can't do it.
伙计们!
Boys
我们上
We're going in.
嗨...
Hi.
这不是个高兴的问候!
Oh,that is not a happy"Hi."
卡萝怀孕了
Carol's pregnant.
我找到了
Oh, I found it.
什,什,什么?
Well, what? What?
耶
Yeah.
你（的表情）再保持这样两小时
Do that for another two hours
就会变成我现在这样
you might be where I am right about now.
这样的话 枕头的事就可先放在一旁?是不是?
Kind of puts that whole pillow thing in perspective, huh, Mon?
你打算怎么处理（面对）整件事?
Well, now, how do you fit into this whole thing?
卡萝说她和苏珊想让我加人
Well, Carol says she and Susan want me to be involved.
但是对这件事我不太感到舒服, 我不想卷进去
But if I'm not comfortable with it, I don't have to be involved.
一切由我做决定
Basically, it's totally up to me.
她人好好 我真想念她
She is so great. I miss her.
她所谓的"加入"代表什么?
What does she mean by "involved"?
我猜,你大部分的工作已经结束了
I mean, presumably, the biggest part of your job is done.
总之 她们要我和她们去做
Anyway, they want me to go down to this
B超检查
sonogram thing with them tomorrow.
罗斯!你打算怎么做?
So, what are you gonna do?
我也不知道
I have no idea.
不管我怎么做 我还是孩子的爹
No matter what I do, though, I'm still gonna be a father.
面已经被搅乱了 不是吗?
Well, this is still ruined, right?
玛莎路金的女儿会打电话给你
Oh. Martha Lugwin's daughter is gonna call you.
怎么会有咖哩味?
Mm. What's that curry taste?
因为有放咖哩
Curry.
嗯
Mm.
这东西很好吃 真的
I think they're great. I really do.
你还记得路金一家人?
You remember the Lugwins?
他们的大女儿喜欢你  对不?
The big one had a thing for you, didn't she?
他们家的女儿都喜欢他
They all had a thing for him.
不要这样,妈妈
Oh, Mom.
抱歉  她为何要打电话给我?
I'm sorry. Why is this girl going to call me?
她刚毕业 想找份烹饪的工作吧
Oh, she just graduated, and she wants to be something in cooking or food
可能
or I don't know.
我告诉她你开了一家餐馆
Anyway, I told her you had a restaurant, so...
不 妈 我没开餐馆 我在餐厅工作
No, Mom. I don't have a restaurant. I work in a restaurant.
呃 他们不需要知道
Well, they don't have to know that.
罗斯  能帮我做义大利面吗?
Ross, could you come and help me with the spaghetti.
好的
Yes.
我们吃意大利面呀 那也太
Oh, we're having spaghetti. That's...
简单了
easy.
我知道这样要求过于自私
I know this is going to sound unbelievably selfish on my part
你能不能和他们说一下
but were you planning on bringing up
小孩 女同性恋之类的事?
the whole baby lesbian thing?
因为这样可以让我喘口气
Because I think it might take some of the heat off me.
瑞秋到底怎么了? 我们在俱乐部遇见她父母
What that Rachel did to her life? We ran into her parents at the club.
他们很不开心
They were not playing very well.
我不想讲他们为此婚礼花了些什么
I'm not gonna tell you what they spent on that wedding
但是4万块不是个小数目?
but $40,000 is a lot of money.
但是至少瑞秋还有机会
Well,at least she had the chance
在举行婚礼之际离开那个男人
to leave a man at the altar.
什么意思?      没什么
What's that supposed to mean?        Nothing.
随便说说       不 不是的!
It's an expression.         No, it's not.
别听你妈乱讲话
Don't listen to your mother.
你一直都很独立
You're independent and you always have been.
就连你小时候 胖嘟嘟
Even when you were a kid, and you were chubby
的一个朋友也没有 你还是活得好好的
and you had no friends, you were just fine.
你会待在你房里看书玩拼图
You'd read alone in your room. And your puzzles
而像罗斯这种人则追求卓越
Look, there are people, like Ross, who need to shoot for the stars.
博物馆 发表论文...
With his museum and his papers getting published.
其他人则安于现状
Other people are satisfied with staying where they are.
我告诉你 这种人不会得癌症!
I'm telling you, these are the people who never get cancer.
我还知道 这些女人想拥有一切
And I read about these women trying to have it all, and I thank God
幸好我们家的小摩妮卡 似乎没有这种问题
our little Harmonica doesn't seem to have that problem.
罗斯 你现在过的如何?
So, Ross, what's going on with you?
最近有什么新闻八卦之类
Any stories? No news,
可以和老爸老妈分享的
no little anecdotes to share with the folks?
好吧
Okay, okay.
我知道你们想了解
Ahem. Look, I, uh I realize you guys have been wondering
我和卡萝之间倒底怎么了
what exactly happened between Carol and me.
事情是这样的
And so, well, here's the deal.
卡萝是个Les
Carol's a lesbian.
她和一个名字苏珊的女人同居
She's living with a woman named Susan.
她怀了我的孩子
She's pregnant with my child.
并打算和苏珊共同抚养他
And she and Susan are going to raise the baby.
这些你全都知道?
And you knew about this?
你的状况真的很糟糕吗?
Your folks are really that bad, huh?
你要知道这些人十分专业,
Well, you know, these people are pros.
他们会躲在那里
They know what they're doing. They take their time.
再来个突然袭击
They get the job done.
常言道：父母是无法交换的
Boy, I know they say that you can't change your parents.
如果可以 我要你的父母
Boy, if you could, I'd want yours.
我要去尿尿了
Must pee.
如果你是双胞胎 情况会更惨
You know, it's even worse when you're twins.
你是双胞胎?      对 我们不往来
You're a twin?         Oh, yeah. We don't speak.
她是一心追求事业的人
She's like this highpowered, driven, careertype.
她从事什么工作?      服务生
What does she do?         She's a waitress.
各位 我得打扫了
All right. You guys, I kind of gotta clean up now.
钱德 你是独子? 你没有这些困扰?
Chandler, you're an only child, right? You don't have any of this.
没有 尽管我有个想像中的朋友
Well, no, although I did have an imaginary friend
而我爸妈比较喜欢他
who my parents actually preferred.
帮我把灯关了
Hit the lights, please.
我在里面多久了?
How long was I in there?
只是我要打扫了
I'm just cleaning up.
需要帮忙吗?
Oh, do you, uh? Do you need any help?
好呀 谢了
Um, okay, sure. Thanks.
不管怎样!
Anyway
明天要见巴瑞 紧张吗?
So you nervous about Barry tomorrow?
有一点
Oh, a little. Mmhm.
很紧张
A lot. Mmhm.
有任何建议吗?
So got any advice?
就一个最近刚被甩的人而言
You know, as someone who's recently been dumped.
你应该避免用"甩"这个字眼
Well, you may want to steer clear of the word "dumped."
现在他可能痛不欲生
Chances are he's going to be this broken shell of a man. You know?
因此你不该显得艳光照人
So you should try not to look too terrific.
我知道这一点很难做到
I know it'll be hard.
这样吧 我拿戒指还巴瑞
Or, you know, hey, I'll go down there, and I'll give Barry back his ring.
你陪卡萝及苏珊去做检查
And you can go with Carol and Susan to the OBGYN.
你明天得见卡萝
You've got Carol tomorrow.
这事怎么就变得这么复杂?
When did it get so complicated?
你可问倒我了
Got me.
还记得我们在高中时代吗?      记得
Remember when we were in high school?         Yeah.
你没想过自己会遇见心上人
I mean, didn't you think you' were gonna meet someone
谈恋爱 然后厮守终生吗?
fall in love, and that'd be it?
罗斯?      什么事?
Ross?         Yes, yes.
没想到自己会沦落到这个地步
Oh. Man. I never thought I'd be here.
我也是
Me neither.
抱歉 我迟到了
Hi. Sorry I'm late. I got stuck at work.
我忙得无法脱身恐龙之类的事
There was this big dinosaur thing. Anyway
嗨
Hi.
罗斯 记得苏珊吗?      我怎么会忘记
Ross, you remember Susan.         How could I forget?
罗斯
Ross.
苏珊,你好 她的手好有力
Hello, Susan. Good shake, good shake.
那么我们在等...
So, uh, we're just waiting for?
欧伯曼大夫      欧伯曼大夫他
Dr. Oberman.         Dr. Oberman. Okay, and is he?
她      当然,"她"
She.        Of course, "she."
她了解我们的特殊状况?
She,uh,familiar with our special situation?
了解 而且她非常支持
Yes,and she's very supportive.
这太好了
Great. Okay, that's great. Heh.
不,我只是
No, I'm...
谢了
Thanks.
呱 呱
Quack, quack
呱 呱 呱
quack, quack, quack.
罗斯
Ross?
那是用来打开我的子宫颈的
That opens my cervix.
巴瑞      进来
Barry?        Come on in.
没问题?
Are you sure?
没问题, 罗此得待在这儿好几个小时
It's fine, it's fine. Robbie's gonna be here for hours.
呃
Huh?
那么!最近好吗?
So how are you doing?
我...
I'm...
我很好
I'm okay.
你的气色好极了
You look great.
耶 那个
Yeah, well
法大夫 杰森快没气了
Dr. Farber,Jason Greenspan's gagging.
马上到 我马上回来
Be right there. I'll be back in a second.
我甩了他
I dumped him.
是的
Okay.
啊
Oh!
罗斯      我是说 我们
Ross.         So, um? So how's this going to work
以后怎么办?
ahem,you know,with us?
比方说某些重大的决定
You know,when,like,important decisions have to be made?
给我举个例子!
Give me a "for instance."
我也不知道!比如?
Well, I don't know. Okay, okay.
比方说孩子的名字      马龙
How about with the baby's name?         Marlon
如果是个男孩 如果是个女孩就叫米妮
Marlon. if it's a boy. Minnie, if it's a girl.
和米奇的女友同名?
As in "Mouse"?
和我奶奶同名
As in my grandmother.
不管怎样,听到这个还是想到米老鼠
Still, you say "Minnie," you hear "Mouse."
那
How about, um...
朱莉亚如何?
How about "Julia"?
朱莉亚?
Julia?
我们决定用米妮
We agreed on Minnie.
真幽默我们曾决定共同生活一辈子
It's funny, um, we agreed we'd spend our lives together.
世事难料 兵来将挡
Things change. Roll with the punches.
茱莉亚 就这么决定
I believe Julia's on the table.
抱歉
Oh. Sorry about that.
近来可好?
So, what have you been up to?
还行
Oh. Not much.
我刚找到工作      这太好了
I got a job.        Hey, that's great.
你为何晒得这么黑?
Why are you so tan?
哦 我 呃
Oh, I, uh...
我到阿鲁巴了
I went to Aruba.
你自己一个去渡蜜月?
Oh, no. You went on our honeymoon alone?
不是
No.
我和...
See, uh, I went with...
也许会很不好受      我?
Now, this may hurt.         Me?
不是
No.
我和明蒂去了
I went with Mindy.
明蒂?
Mindy?
我的伴娘明蒂?
My maid of honor, Mindy?
对 我们是认真的
Yeah, well, we're kind of a thing now.
呃
Well, I'm
你去做植发了?
You got plugs?
小心 还不固定
Careful,careful.They haven't quite taken yet.
你还配了隐形眼镜
And you got lenses.
你不是讨厌将手指放进眼睛吗?
But you hate sticking your finger in your eye.
还不是为了她
Not for her.
哦
Oh.
我真的得感谢你
Listen, I really wanted to thank you.
嗯
Okay.
一个月前我想伤害你
About a month ago, I wanted to hurt you...
我从未如此激动过
...more than I've ever wanted to hurt anyone in my life.
我是个整牙医师
And I'm an orthodontist.
哇
Wow.
你说得没错 我以为我们会过得很快乐
You know, you were right. I mean, I thought we were happy.
我们不快乐
We weren't happy.
但是和明蒂在一起
But with Mindy
现在我很快乐
now I'm happy.
吐掉      什么?
Spit.         What?
对我说呢
Me.
无论如何 呃
Anyway, um...
总之 这东西属于你的!
I guess, uh I guess this belongs to you.
谢谢你送我
And thank you for giving it to me.
谢谢你送还给我
Well, thank you for giving it back.
喂!
Hello.
拜托 海伦有什么不好?
Oh, please. What's wrong with Helen?
海伦盖勒?
Helen Geller?
我不同意!      她不会叫海伦盖勒的
I don't think so.         Hello, it's not gonna be Helen Geller.
谢谢
Thank you.
不 我是说她不姓盖勒
No. I mean, it's not Geller.
难道她叫海伦威利克
What, it's gonna be Helen Willick?
老实说 我们考虑用海伦威利克班奇
No, actually, um, we talked about Helen Willick Bunch.
等等 为何有她的份?
Well, wait a minute. Why is she in the title?
因为她也是我的宝宝
Because it's my baby too.
是吗? 我不记得女人也会制造精子
That's funny. Really? I don't remember you making any sperm.
我们都知道那是个极大的挑战
And we all know what a challenge that is.
呃 清楚没?      够了 你们两个 别吵了
Uhhuh. See?        All right, you two, stop it.
不 功劳全让她抢了 我也在场
No, no. She gets a credit. Hey, I'm in there too.
罗斯  你该不会想用海伦威利克班奇盖勒吧?
Honestly. You're not actually suggesting Helen Willick Bunch Geller.
因为这有虐待儿童之嫌
I think that borders on child abuse.
当然没有 我想用盖勒威利克班奇
Of course not. I'm suggesting Geller Willick Bunch.
绝对不行 你看他
Oh, no. No, no, no. You see what he's doing?
没人会叫她全名的
He knows no one is gonna say all those names.
他知道别人只会叫她盖勒 这样他就得逞了
He knows they'll wind up calling her Geller. Then he gets his way.
我得逞? 你认为这样算我得逞?
My way? You think this is my way?
相信我  我没想到自己会沦落到这种地步
Believe me, of all the ways I ever imagined this moment in my life being
这不是我想要的 我是不得已的...
this is not my way. You know what? This is too hard.
有人在吗? 今天如何 想呕吐吗?
Knock, knock. How are we today? Any nausea?
只是一点点      一点点
A little.         Just a little.
我只是问准妈妈 很感谢你们的分享
Well, I was just wondering about the mothertobe, but, uh, thanks for sharing.
躺好
Uh, lie back.
知道吗?我不加入了
You know what? I'm gonna go.
我认为此时自己无法淌这坛浑水
Um, I don't think I can be involved in this particular family thing.
我的天呀
Oh, my God.
看啊
Look at that.
我知道
I know.
很神奇吧
Well, isn't that amazing?
我们该看到什么?
What are we supposed to be seeing here?
我不知道 我认为它将要攻击企业号
I don't know, but I think it's about to attack the Enterprise.
如果你们把头稍微向左偏 两眼放轻松
You know, if you tilt your head to the left and relax your eyes...
它样子就像是一个颗老马铃薯
it kind of looks like an old potato.
那么就不要那么干
Then don't do that, all right?
摩妮卡
Monica?
你认为呢?
What do you think?
嗯
Mmhm...
你哭了?
Are you welling up?
才没呢!      你在哭
No.         You are.
你有 眼泪都下来了      我没有
You are. You're welling up.         No, I'm not.
你就要成为阿姨了      闭嘴!
You're gonna be an aunt.         Oh, shut up.
你好 明蒂
Hi, Mindy.
我是瑞秋
Hi, it's Rachel.
我很好 我今天和巴瑞见面了
Yeah, I'm fine. I saw Barry today.
不 他告诉我了
Oh, yeah, yeah, he told me.
没关系 真的
No, it's okay. Really, it's okay.
我诚心祝福你们幸福快乐
I hope you two are very happy. I really do.
如果一切顺利
And, Min, you know, if everything works out
你们结婚生子
and you guys end up getting married and having kids and everything
希望他有他的秃顶和你的鼻子
I just hope they have his old hairline and your old nose.
我知道这招很损!但是现在我感觉好多了
Okay, I know it was a cheap shot, but I feel so much better now.
【海盗美剧 友情制作】
-== http://www.hdmeiju.com ==-
新浪微博：@海盗美剧